iccu19cricketworldcup.com 2012-10-21

# International Cricket Council - Privacy Policy

ICC Development (International) Limited ("us", "our" or "we") is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to our website at [www.icc-cricket.com](http://www.icc-cricket.com/) (the "Website"). Before you proceed with use of the Website, please read the following privacy policy (the "Policy") carefully to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us.

Please be aware that this Policy only governs our use of personally identifiable information that is collected when you are on the Website. This Policy does not extend to the use of data submitted to or through any third party websites to which links may be provided on the Website, and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other websites in order that you understand how they collect, use and share information.

 **Information that we may collect from you**

In general, you can access and browse the Website without providing personal information. However, there may be times when we will request personally identifiable information from you in order that you may participate in the Website's services, activities or features. The personally identifiable information collected may include (without limitation) your fist name, last name, e-mail address, address, country of residence, nationality, gender, date of birth, preferences, billing address, credit or debit card information, account name, account password, answer to security question and/or mother's maiden name. We may also collect information about your usage of the Website as well as information about you from messages you post to any forum or message board and emails, letters and other communications you may send to us from time to time.

When you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Website, you agree that such information may be stored and processed by us and/or on our behalf. We may also collect information about your interaction with the Website and the services on the Website. We receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information (see further below) and the page(s) you requested. In particular, we reserve the right to perform statistical analysis of user behaviours and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Website and to ascertain the number of users that have visited particular pages of the Website. We will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties, and such statistical data will not identify any individual.

Please note that if you submit your personally identifiable information to us, you will be giving your consent to the transfer of such information outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). Collected information is processed in India, and may be stored and used elsewhere depending on the location of affiliates, business partners and other entities who are permitted to access such information under the terms of this Policy. Organisations based in some countries outside of the EEA may not protect privacy and personal data rights as extensively as those based and/or regulated within the EEA (and such locations may include countries which may not afford the same level of protection of such data as the country from which you provided the information).

 **Use of your information**

We collect and use your information in order to give you a better service and to provide you with information you request, including information about ICC events and/or the sport of cricket. Your information is also used to fulfil your requests for certain services and/or to participate in certain activities and make the Website more useful to you. Where you have consented when providing us with your details, we may also allow carefully selected third parties to contact you from time to time about events, products and services which may be of interest to you

You have the right to prevent marketing information being sent direct to you, whether by us or by our carefully selected third parties. If you prefer not to receive information from us or from any other organisation to which we may wish to disclose your personal information, ensure that you tick the appropriate box which appears where you are submitting your personal data. If you change your mind, at any time, about being contacted by us or our third parties, please let us know. Please understand that where you have opted out of receiving further communications, it may take us a few days to process your request.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information without your express consent where we believe disclosure to be required by law or regulation, or necessary to protect or defend our rights or property, the safety of the public and/or the users of the Website.

 **Cookies**

In common with many other website operators, we may use standard technology called 'cookies' on the Website. Cookies are small amounts of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to improve the Website, to monitor Website traffic and to deliver a better and more personalised service for you. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser setting to prevent cookies being stored. However, if you adjust your browser setting in this way, you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website.

Other companies that are advertising on our Website may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Policy. Such third party advertisers do not have access to our cookies.

 **Children under 16**

If you are under 16, you must obtain the approval of your parent or legal guardian before sending us any of your personal information (such as your name, e-mail address, home address, date of birth, etc).

 **Security and data retention**

We employ security measures to help safeguard the information we collect from you on the Website, including technical and organisational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorised access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorised third parties will never be able to access or use your personal information for improper purposes. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

 **Changes to this Policy**

This Policy was last updated on [insert publication date]. We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. Any changes in the future will be posted to the Website. Accordingly, we recommend that you check this page periodically in order to review our current Policy.

 **Accessing, updating or removing your information**

You have the right to receive a copy of and/or update, modify and/or remove the personal information that we hold about you. If you wish to receive a copy of the personal information that we hold about you, please let us know. We may charge a small fee towards the cost of administering your request. If you believe that any of the personal information that we hold about you has changed or is incorrect, you may ask us to change or update such data.

All requests shall be in writing and shall be directed to the contact details as set out below and shall include enough information to enable us to satisfy ourselves as to your identity.

 **Contacting us**

You can contact us by emailing us at [enquiry@icc-cricket.com](mailto:enquiry@icc-cricket.com) or by writing to us at the following address:

ICC Development (International) Limited  
Street 69, Dubai Sports City  
Emirates Road  
PO Box 500 070  
Dubai  
United Arab Emirates

© Copyright 2010 - ICC Development (International) Limited. All rights reserved.
